(+49) 1522 2441871 Stuttgart, Germany ning.gao@de.bosch.com

Ning Gao

Doctoral Researcher

Date of birth: 29.05.1992 Place of birth: Jilin, China

linkedin.com/in/ning-gao-9245a0165

I'm a fourth year PhD student at Autonomous Learning Robots (ALR) at KIT supervised by Prof. Gerhard Neumann. I'm also a doctoral researcher at Bosch Center for Artificial Intelligence (BCAI), Renningen, Germany. My research interests lie in the field of Meta-Learning and representation learning on Robot Perception & Manipulation.

SKILLS

Languages Python, C++, Bash, SQL, ŁTĘX, MarkDown

Tools Git, ROS, Blender

Communication Chinese (native), English, German

WORK EXPERIENCE

Researcher	May 2020 — Present
Bosch Center for Artificial Intelligence	Renningen, Germany
Meta-Learning, Representation Learning, Robot Manipulation	
Markey There's Charlest	May 2010 Oct 2010

Master Thesis StudentMay 2019 — Oct 2019Bosch Center for Artificial IntelligenceRenningen, GermanyBenchmarking deep learning algorithms for 6DoF object pose estimation

Research InternOct 2018 — Feb 2019Bosch Corporate ResearchRenningen, Germany

Driver's gaze estimation for autonomous driving

Research InternMar 2018 — Aug 2018Bosch Corporate ResearchRenningen, Germany

Build interior camera system prototype for autonomous driving

Undergraduate Research AssistantNov 2017 — May 2018Institute of Measurement and Control Systems (MRT), KITKarlsruhe, Germany

Joint tracking for multiple pedestrians and vehicles

Summer InternJun. 2015 — Sep. 2015Daimler Greater China Ltd.Beijing, China

Engine testing and calibration

EDUCATION

Doctoral Researcher in Computer Science	2020-Present
Karlsruhe Institute of Technology, Karlsruhe, Germany	
M.Sc in Mechanical Engineering	2016-2019
Karlsruhe Institute of Technology, Karlsruhe, Germany	
B.Sc in Automotive Engineering	2011-2016
Tongji University, Shanghai	
Outstanding Graduate Award	
Daqing Experimental Highschool	2008-2011
Daqing, Heilongjiang Province	

ACTIVITIES

Reviewer of ICRA2021, ICRA2022, IROS2022, CoRL2022, CoRL2023
The Machine Learning Summer School, Tübingen, Germany 2020

PUBLICATIONS

What Matters for Meta-Learning Vision Regression Tasks? CVPR 2022

Gao, Ning and Ziesche, Hanna Carolin and Anh Vien, Ngo and Volpp, Michael and Neumann, Gerhard

Signature: Datum: